OP
ED
Mail received
真城君
Mashiro...
「やりました「PCP」一話目本ちゃん1位を獲りました」
Mashiro Moritaka
We did it
First chapter of PCP got 1st place!
Does that get us a bit closer to our dream?
We did it!
PCP's first chapter got 1st place in the rankings!
First chapter of PCP got 1st place!
Does that get us a bit closer to our dream?
「少しは２人の夢に近づけたかな」
大丈夫 きっと近づいてるよ 私たち
We'll be fine.
We're definitely getting closer to our dream.
ano ne moshimo ima sugu ni kimi no moto he to
Hey, if I could go to where you are right now
ikeru naraba kono koe ga nakunattemo ii ya
then I could accept losing my voice
mezasu basho ga amari ni mo tooku
The goals I've set myself seem impossible to reach,
boku wa mou michi ni mayoisou da
and I feel lost on my path
kowareta jishaku wo ate ni shiteru n da
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in another's shadow
dareka no kage ni kakurete sa
nanika wo te ni ireru tame nanika wo tebanasu nante koto wo
If we keep letting go of some things in order to find something else,
tsuzukete mo kitto bokura wa otona ni wa narenai
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
narenai
Never
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神字幕组---
台本:共由先生         翻译:   poopy    虫
校对：绫女      后期：福尔摩斯的手杖
Tenacity and Determination
いいですか 「+NATURAL」をジャック一
Are we clear?
+NATURAL will be the best manga in Jack.
いえ 日本一のマンガにします 「PCP」に負けるなんてもっての外
No, in all of Japan.
Losing to PCP is out of the question!
だ…大丈夫ですよ こっちは４月からアニメも始まる事ですし
I-It'll be okay.
We've got an anime starting this April, after all.
ああ そうだ
Oh, right.
これ 預かってきました
I was given this to show you.
アニメの１６話から登場する三宮沙也乃役の候補です
Candidates for the role of Mimiya Sayano, who appears starting in episode 16.
４名ほどいるので 原作者側の意見を聞きたいと
Since there are four applicants, they wanted the opinion of the authors.
新妻君にも 次の打ち合わせの時に返事をもらう事にしてるんで 岩瀬君も
I'll get Niizuma's opinion the next time we meet.
この亜豆美保って 私が中学３年の時の同級生です
And you—
Azuki Miho...
We were classmates in my third year of middle school.
えっ ほんとに そんな偶然って
What, really?
What a coincidence.
あっ この子 真城君の彼女
Azuki Miho
aaaa
Filmography:
Birthday:
Data:
POB:
5/11/1993
height 162cm, weight 44kg
Saitama, currently lives in Tokyo
She's Mashiro's girlfriend.
えっ 彼女
Girlfriend?
うん 真城君が入院してた時 何度もお見舞いに来てたから
She visited him several times when he was in the hospital.
亜豆美保 真城最高 高木秋人
Azuki Miho
Azuki Miho.
Mashiro Moritaka
Mashiro Moritaka.
Takagi Akito
Takagi Akito.
亜城木夢叶
Ashirogi Mutou
Ashirogi Mutou!
１話目１位 最高のスタートだね
The first chapter is number one!
You're off to a great start!
ああ このあとも上位をキープできるように 頑張らないと
Yeah. Now we have to keep
working hard to maintain a high rank.
そのためには キャラが弱いって点を克服しないとな
For that, we have to overcome the weak points of the characters!
でも 舞をスポーツ万能にするのはやりすぎかな
But is making Mai athletic overdoing it?
ヒロインなんだし そのくらいのがいいって
She's a heroine. That much is expected.
そうそう
Right, right.
誰から
Who is it?
港浦さんからだ
It's Miura.
ああ 真城君
Oh, Mashiro?
亜豆美保ちゃんって 中学の同級生で 確か真城君の
As I recall, Azuki Miho went to middle school with you, and she's your...
あっ はい
君の通ってた中学 どんだけすごい学校だったんだ
Uh, yes.
Just how amazing is your middle school?
亜城木君に秋名君 それに亜豆美保ちゃんは声優
There's Ashirogi and Akina, and Azuki Miho is a voice actress...
実績も結構あって びっくりしたよ
She's pretty accomplished, too. I was surprised.
あの…何で亜豆美保さんの話が
Um, why are we talking about Azuki Miho?
その美保ちゃん 「+NATURAL」のヒロイン役 三宮沙也乃役の最終候補に残ってるぞ
Because she's an applicant for the role of
Mimiya Sayano, the heroine of +NATURAL.
沙也乃役の候補
An applicant for the role of Sayano?!
何だ 知らなかったのか
What, you didn't know?
来週の土曜に オーディションだ 応援してやれよ じゃあな
The audition is next Saturday.
I'm rooting for her.
See ya.
亜豆が「NATURAL」に 何で
Azuki in NATURAL...
サイコー
Why?
Saikou.
何 今の電話 美保の事話してなかった
What was that all about?
Were you talking about Miho?
Yeah.
何で港浦さんが亜豆の事で電話してくるんだよ
Why did Miura call about Azuki?
亜豆が沙也乃役の候補になったって
He said that Azuki is an applicant for the role of Sayano.
沙也乃って
"Sayano"?
この子だよ 「NATURAL」のヒロイン役
This girl.
NATURAL's heroine.
これって 岩瀬と新妻さんの
Isn't this Iwase and Niizuma's manga?!
来週の土曜に オーディションなんだって
He said the audition's next Saturday.
それで 港浦さんが
So that's why he...
うん 担当だし 単純に「声優だったんだ すごいな」って
Yeah. He's their editor, after all.
He just called to say how amazing it is that she's a voice actress.
な…何で 美保そんな役 受けてんの
Wh-Why is Miho auditioning for that character?
美保は 「PCP」がアニメになったら安之城舞役やるじゃん
She's supposed to play the role of
Annojo Mai when PCP becomes an anime!
沙也乃役って 出てきたのは遅いけど
Sayano gets introduced late,
他に目立った女の子のキャラ 出てないし
but there are no other female characters that stand out.
これからの展開次第では 押しも押されぬヒロインに
Given how the events unfold, she's sure to become the main heroine.
え 美保は亜城木夢叶のヒロインやるんだから 他でやっちゃ駄目
What?
Miho's going to be the heroine for
Ashirogi Mutou. She can't be anyone else's!
よりによって ライバルと思ってる岩瀬新妻コンビのマンガじゃん
Especially not for the manga created by your rivals, Iwase and Niizuma!
ありえない 真城 止めなよ
No way!
Mashiro, stop her!
いや
No.
大きな役ほど亜豆のキャリアになる
The bigger the role, the better for her career.
でも 真城のマンガがアニメになって
But...
What happened to your dream of getting married
after Miho stars in the anime adaptation of your manga?
美保が ヒロインを演じたら結婚するっていう２人の夢は
仕事は仕事
A job is a job.
結婚は 俺は マンガ 亜豆は声優を全力でやっていったその先にある
Marriage comes after we do our best at manga and voice acting, respectively.
今は エイジと岩瀬「NATURAL」に先に行かれてるんだ しかたない
Right now, Iwase and Eiji are doing better than us with NATURAL.
That's just how it s.
何言ってんの 話違わない
What are you saying? Don't you think this is wrong?!
絶対おかしいって
That's messed up—
香耶ちゃん
何
Kaya.
What?
香耶ちゃんが口出す事じゃないだろ
It's none of your business.
ひどい みんなの事思って言ってるのに
How mean.
I just want what's best for everyone...
気持ちは分かるけど 俺たちがここでとやかく言っても な
I understand how you feel, but it's not our place to say anything.
でも
But...
サイコーの前であんな言い方しても駄目だ
You can't say things like that in front of Saikou.
サイコーだって 本心は出てほしくないって思ってるはずだ
I don't think he really wants her to do it, either.
でも 亜豆が選んだ仕事なら それを止めるなんてサイコーはしない
But he won't stop her from doing work that she's chosen to do.
何で
Why not?
意地
He's stubborn!
意地か ちょっと分かる 真城 そういうところ素直じゃないよね
Stubborn, huh? I can see that.
He's not very honest when it comes to things like this.
亜豆も かわいくないよな
Neither is Azuki.
そうよね 何で沙也乃役に
For sure.
But why did she audition for Sayano?
普通 「真城君のライバルのアニメなんて私できない」だよな
You'd think she'd say, "I can't be in an anime by Mashiro's rival!"
でも 亜豆はそういうタイプじゃない
But she's not that type of girl.
うん 「仕事なんだから頑張る」とか言いそう
She'd just say "It's a job, so I have to do my best."
亜豆の仕事なんだから 止めるなら亜豆の方
It's her job offer, so it's up to her to decide.
明日 ２人で亜豆の所へ行ってみようぜ
Let's go to her house tomorrow.
O-Okay.
２人とも いらっしゃい
Welcome, you two!
お…お久しぶりです
It's been a while.
すみません 急に押しかけちゃって
Sorry for coming on such short notice.
いいのよ 聞きたい事 いっぱいあったから さあ 上がって
It's fine. I have so much to ask you!
Come on, come in.
聞きたい事って
Ask us?
そう でも何で その話を
I see.
But how did you hear about this?
たまたま「NATURAL」の担当さんから 俺たちの耳に入って
We happened to hear it from NATURAL's editor.
何で引き受けたの
Why are you auditioning?
応募は 社長が勝手に
My manager sent in the application on his own...
あっ そうなんだ
I see. And you passed.
で 通っちゃったんだ
オーディションは いつ
Yeah.
When's the audition?
今度の土曜日 １時から
This Saturday...
at 1 PM.
どこで
渋谷近くのスタジオ
Where?
A studio near Shibuya.
どうする気
What will you do?
やめた方がいいって 受かっちゃったら やばいじゃん
Huh?
You shouldn't do it!
It'd be horrible if you pass!
もし亜豆さんが沙也乃役に決まったら
If you land the role of Sayano,
俺たちの作品が アニメ化になった時 どうするんだよ
what will you do when our work becomes an anime?
同じ「ジャック」作品で ヒロインの声優が かぶる事になる
That would make you the heroine in two Jack productions.
いくら作者の俺たちが推しても「NATURAL」でやってるからって事になるだろ
No matter how hard Mashiro and I push for you,
they'll just say "She's already doing NATURAL."
真城君も そう言ってる
Mashiro said that?
真城は相変わらず 美保の仕事だから美保が決める事って言い張ってる
Mashiro's the same as ever. He's keeps insisting
that it's up to you to decide since it's your job.
そう
I see.
サイコーは ああいうやつだから 気持ちも分かるけど 俺は出てほしくない
That's just how he is.
I know how he feels, but I don't want you to do this.
高木君
Takagi?
俺たちの作品が すぐアニメになる保証なんてないけど
There's no guarantee that our manga will become an anime anytime soon,
亜豆さんは 俺たちの作品がアニメになった時のヒロイン
but you'll be the heroine when it does.
アニメは 「NATURAL」だけじゃないじゃん
NATURAL's not the only anime out there!
わざわざ夢が遠ざかる事するのおかしいよ
You shouldn't do something that
takes you further away from your dream!
意地張るのはやめて素直になって
Don't be so stubborn. Be honest with yourself!
香耶
美保がオーディション受けないって言えば 真城 絶対 喜ぶって
Kaya...
If you say you won't go to the audition, Mashiro will definitely be happy!
そうだな 亜豆さんがそう言えば サイコーは ホッとする
That's right.
If you say that, Saikou will be relieved.
もし逆に 「受けないでくれ」っ言われたら 亜豆さん うれしいだろ
If he told you not to go, you'd be happy, right?
そうそう
That's right!
２人とも 意地張りすぎ とにかく 「ジャック」作品のヒロインは やらない
The two of you are too stubborn.
In any case, you should at least decide to avoid major roles
そのくらいは 決めておくべき
in any Jack anime adaptation from here on out!
まあ サイコーが言うように 亜豆さんの仕事だから亜豆さんが決める事
Well, like Saikou says, it's your
work, so it's up to you to decide.
でも 「真城君が止めなかったから」っていうのを理由に受けるのだけは やめてほしい
But I don't want you to accept the role just because Mashiro didn't stop you.
分かった 今日 真城君にメールで相談してみる
I understand.
I'll text him today and ask.
えっ だから 真城に言っても もう何て答えるか分かってんじゃん
Huh? But you know exactly what he'll say!
香耶ちゃん 俺たちはここまで あとは亜豆さんとサイコーが決め事
Kaya, we've done all we can.
The rest is for Azuki and Saikou to decide.
帰ろうぜ
Let's go.
なんか煮えきらない
But we didn't get anywhere!
いいから
Come on.
秋人さん
Akito!
亜豆さん またな
See you later, Azuki!
亜豆が沙也乃役に くそ
Azuki voicing Sayano...
Damn it!
New mail
Azuki Miho
亜豆
Azuki!
aaaaaaaaaa
Azuki Miho
Good evening
Are we stubborn?
意地っ張り…か
Stubborn, huh?
Mail received
aaaaaaaaaa
Mashiro Moritaka
Re: Good evening
I dunno.
よし 1ページ目 終了
Mashiro
All right! First page, done!
続けてバリバリやるわよ
Let's keep up the good work!
香耶ちゃん もうちょっと静かに
Kaya, can't you be a bit quieter?
え 何で テンション上げていかないと
Huh? Why?
I have to keep everyone's spirits up!
みんなが集中できないだろ
You're making it hard for them to concentrate.
真城先生
Mashiro.
はい
３ページ目のこのコマなんですが
Yes?
This panel on the third page...
先生の背景のアタリだと 人物と 若干パースに狂いが発生します
In this rough sketch of the scenery, the
perspective on the characters is a bit off.
えっ ちょっと貸して下さい
Let me see.
うん 確かに
You're right.
すみません すぐ直します
I'll fix it right away.
森屋さん 相変わらずですね
Moriya's the same as ever.
いえ 今週は僕も変だと思います
No.
I think something's off this week, too.
僕も気になる所は直せる範囲で直してますが いつもより多い気がします
Huh?
I can fix the mistakes I'm finding,
but there are more than usual this week.
そ そう
R-Really?
はい
Yes.
明日の原稿アップまでに 直しきれれば いいんですけど
I just hope we can fix them all before we have to turn in the manuscript tomorrow.
「PCP」本ちゃんも２位だ
PCP came in 2nd.
「CROW」３位 「NATURAL」５位
CROW was 3rd, and NATURAL was 5th.
やった
All right!
今日は６時に原稿受け取りに行くけど
I'll come over at 6 to pick up the manuscript.
分かりました
Okay!
あと 「NATURAL」は１か月後に アニメが始まる
And the NATURAL anime will start in a month.
絶対 気を抜くなって
He told us not to get comfortable!
２話目が２位なら大丈夫だ 手応えがある
We're safe if our second chapter is in 2nd place.
It's a good response from the readers.
あるのに 「NATURAL」の沙也乃役に 亜豆か
It is, but...
Azuki voicing Sayano in NATURAL...
本当に これでいいのか
Am I really okay with that?
オーディションは 明日
Start
The audition is tomorrow.
サイコー
えっ ああ よかったな この調子で頑張ろうぜ
Saikou...
Oh, that's great.
Let's keep it up.
コピー 取れてっぞ
You already made copies.
あ 紙１枚 無駄にしちゃった
Ah... I wasted a sheet of paper.
俺 亜豆に 「オーディション受けても」
I told Azuki that she shouldn't go to the
audition just because you won't stop her.
「サイコーが止めなかったから」って言うのはやめろ」って言っておいたからな
な…何で
Wh-Why?
余計な事して悪いと思ってるけど
I feel bad for butting in, but...
いや サンキュ
No.
Thanks...
話は これまでどおり面白い
The story's good, as usual.
だが どうしたんだ 真城君
But Mashiro, what's wrong?
絵に いつものような繊細さが感じられない こんな事では
I can't feel your usual delicacy in the art.
服部さん 真城は
This won't—
Hattori!
Mashiro!
すみません
I'm sorry. Is it still possible to make revisions?
今から修正させてもらえますか
分かった と言いたいところだが
I'd like to say "okay", but I've got a meeting in three hours.
３時間後に 人と会う約束がある
まあ この話数は これで預かっていくよ
It's only a few pages, so I'll just take it as is.
すみません ２時間で直しますんで 時間を下さい
Sorry!
I'll fix it in two hours, so please give me some time!
サイコー 俺も手伝う 何でも言って
Saikou!
I'll help with anything. Tell me what to do.
いや シュージンは 完璧な話を作ったんだ
No.
You created a perfect story.
だから 絵を完璧にするのは俺の仕事
So it's my job to perfect the art.
それができなきゃプロじゃないんだ
If I can't do that, I can't call myself a pro!
サイコー
Saikou...
亜豆が声優で頑張るのは亜豆のため
Azuki is working hard as a voice actress for her own sake.
意地じゃない 亜豆の事を思って尊重し 信頼してるから
aaaaaaaaaa
Azuki Miho
Good evening
Are we stubborn?
It's not about being stubborn.
Because I care about her, respect her, and trust her,
亜豆が辞退しないなら 僕は止めない
I won't stop her if she doesn't withdraw from the audition.
でも シュージンの言うように 亜豆に結論を押しつけてるだけなのか
But like Shuujin said, maybe it isn't
right to push the decision all onto her.
aaaaaaaaaa
Mashiro Moritaka
Re: Good evening
I dunno.
真城君
Mashiro...
今のセリフ よかったですね
That line was great!
どう 新妻君 誰か気に入った子 いた
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
How about it, Niizuma? Did
anyone's voice catch your attention?
Difficult...
皆さん 上手です 甲乙つけ難いです
They were all good.
It's difficult to make a distinction.
なら 亜豆美保
Then, Azuki Miho—
けど
But.
亜豆美保さんはやめた方がいいと思います
I think it's best to give up on Azuki Miho.
えっ 美保ちゃん 駄目
What? She's no good?
駄目ですよ 真城先生の彼女なんですから
Right. Because she's Mashiro's girlfriend.
僕と秋名さんの作品に出たら 真城先生も高木先生も いい気はしないと思いますけど
If she appears in our work,
I don't think Mashiro and Takagi will be happy about it.
そ そうか そんな事言ってたら 声優なんて
Really?
But she is a voice actress...
まあ 真城君の彼女だから 反対ってのは 無しで
Well, come tomorrow, don't say anything about refusing her because of that.
分かってますけど
I know.
じゃあ 明日 オーディション よろしく頼むよ
Well then, I'll see you at the audition tomorrow.
分かってますけど
I know.
頑張ってね 美保
Good luck, Miho.
うん じゃあ 行ってきます
I'm off, then.
行ってらっしゃい
Take care.
美保 余計な事かもしれないけど
Miho.
This may not be any of my business, but when you're in doubt, be true to your feelings.
迷った時は自分の気持ちに素直にね
意地張ってると嫌われちゃうわよ
People won't like you if you're stubborn!
意地
Stubborn...
オーディション 今日だよね
March
Day
Sat
Sun
Mon
Tues
Wed
Thu
Fri
Sat
Sun
Mon
Manuscript UP
The audition's today.
Yeah.
美保 どうしたかな
I wonder what Miho's doing...
だからもう黙って見守ってろって
Just be quiet and watch over them.
でも
But...
確か１時からって
It was supposed to start at 1 PM.
ほんと うれしい
Really? I'm so happy!
私 頑張る 絶対声優になって 真城君たちのアニメに出る すてき
I'll do my best!
I'll become a voice actress and star in your anime!
It's wonderful!
待ってる
I'll be waiting.
ずっと待ってる
I'll always be waiting.
真城君 頑張ろう 私は真城君を信じる
Mashiro, let's do our best.
I believe in you.
２人の夢を叶えて
Let's make our dream come true.
お 到着
Hachihata Studio
Oh! We're here!
でも ちょっと早く来すぎちゃったかな
But we're a bit early.
レッツ オーディション
LET'S AUDITION!
おはようございます
Good morning.
あっ おはようございます
Oh, good morning.
港浦さん 何階ですか
Miura, what floor is it on?
えっと 確か ２階だ ２階
Uh, let's see... the second floor.
ラジャーです
Roger!
お久しぶりです
It's been a while.
亜城木夢叶
Ashirogi Mutou.
あのペンネームに どんな意味が
What does that pen name mean?
亜豆さんの「亜」 真城君の「城」 高木君の「木」 そして 夢を叶えるって
"A" from Azuki, "shiro" from Mashiro,
"gi" from Takagi,
and "Mutou" from "to grant dreams".
意味は 真城君たちのマンガがアニメになってそのヒロインを私が演じる
It means that their work will become an anime, and I will play the heroine.
それが 私たちの夢
That is our dream!
お ファンタスティックドリームですね
Oh! That's a fantastic dream!
そんな浮ついた考えで マンガを
They made a manga based on that frivolous dream?!
だから 今日は 役を断りに来たんです
That is why I came here today to turn down the role.
ふざけないで
Don't be ridiculous!
今の話を聞いたら
After hearing that story, I'm absolutely determined to use you.
私は あなたをどうしても使いたくなった
沙也乃を最高のヒロインに作り上げてあげるわ
I'll make Sayano into the best heroine possible.
そんな個人の恋愛を理由に断るなんて 私が許さない
I won't allow you to turn it down because of your love life.
断れば 大問題になるわよ
It'll be a huge problem for you if you refuse.
構わない
I don't care.
女の人って こんなに怖いです
Were women always this scary?
うん 怖い
Yes, they are.
真城先生
Mashiro!
行こう
えっ どこへ
Let's go!
Where?
ここから出る
は はい
We're getting out of here!
待ちなさい
O-Okay!
Stop!
こんな事して ただで済むと
Don't think you can get away with this—
真城先生 超かっこいいです 僕に任せて下さい
You're so cool, Mashiro!
Leave it to me!
僕の権限で 美保さんを落とした事にします
On my authority, I will reject her!
誰にも文句は言わせません
I won't let anyone complain about it!
新妻さん ありがとう
Thanks, Niizuma!
ありがとうございます
Thank you!
アイ アイ 愛は勝つ丼です
Love, love!
Love will wiener!
やっちゃったな
I sure did it this time.
でも うれしい
But I'm happy.
亜豆さんの仕事の妨害したのに
Even though I interfered with your work?
私も役 断ったところ
I was about to refuse the role, though.
２人で同じ行動 周波数ぴったりのままだね
We made the same decision.
We were on the exact same wavelength, weren't we?
それに 真城君から 手つないでくれた
And... you held my hand.
えっあっ ごめん えと これは その あの えっと
Ah, sorry! This is, err, um...
離して ごめん
Sorry for letting go.
今日の真城君 頼もしい
You're quite reliable today, Mashiro.
いつもは 頼もしくないですか
Are you saying I'm usually not?
うんマンガの時以外は ちょっとだけ頼りないところあるかも
Yeah. Aside from manga, there are parts of you that are a bit iffy.
意地っ張りだし
And you're stubborn.
それは お互い様
That goes for both of us.
意地っ張りの割に 私たち駄目ね
We're so stubborn and yet we can't even keep a promise.
「夢が叶うまで会わない」が何度目
Just how many times have we seen
each other after we promised not to?
緊急事態だし 残念ながら 現実はこんなもん
It was an emergency.
Unfortunately, life is like that.
真城君 残念なんだ
You're disappointed, Mashiro?
Yeah. I didn't intend to hold hands
with you until our dream came true.
夢が叶うまで 手なんか つなぐつもりなかった
やっぱり すごい意地っ張り
You really are stubborn.
許せない
I won't forgive her!
港浦さん このオーディションのあと すぐ打ち合わせをします
Miura!
We're having a meeting right after this audition.
いいですね
は はい
Understood?
Y-Yes!
早く オーディション 始めましょう
Let's start the auditions now!
新宿から僕は埼京線 亜豆さんは中央線だよね
After Shinjuku, I take the Saikyo line.
You take the Chuo line, right?
うん 会ってから まだ５分もたってないよね 私たち
Yes.
We haven't even been together five minutes...
谷草まで行っていい
Can I go with you to Yakusa?
えっ で…でも僕帰ったら ネームの清書だし
B-But I have to make a clean copy of the storyboard!
だから 電車が谷草に着くまで 着いたら私は帰る
I'll only stay with you until we get to Yakusa.
Then I'll go home.
なんか今日の亜豆さんは 積極的なような
For some reason, Azuki's being pretty bold today...
手 つないじゃったから
Is it because we're holding hands?
分かった 谷草まで この手は離さない
All right! I won't let go of your hand until we reach Yakusa!
今日の真城君 本当に頼もしい
You really are reliable today, Mashiro.
そ そう
R-Really?
Nakamuramachi
Kitayakusa
Minamiyakusa
Funado
入院した時も そうだったけど
This reminds me of when we were in the hospital.
ほんと僕たちって会話ないね
We don't talk much when we're together.
うん でも幸せ
Yeah.
But I'm happy.
次は 南谷草 南谷草です
Next stop is Minamiyakusa. Minamiyakusa.
もう次の駅だ
It's the next stop.
４０分なんて すぐだね
40 minutes went by so quickly.
幸せな時間って たつの早いから
Time always passes quickly when you are happy.
Minamiyakusa
Nakamuramachi
Kitayakusa
じゃあ
Well, then..
真城君
Mashiro.
今度会ったら キスしよう
The next time we meet...
Let's kiss.
どうしちゃったんだ 亜豆 手 つないだから
What's wrong with you, Azuki?
Is it because we held hands?!
だからって そんなに簡単にキス そんなの亜豆らしくないって
Even so, should we be kissing just like that?!
That's not like you!
だから次に会うのは 夢が叶った時
Because the next time we meet... our dream will have come true!
あ 夢が叶うまでは
Until our dream comes true...
やっぱり 亜豆は亜豆だ
Azuki is Azuki, after all.
ただ会っただけじゃないって あの顔
That face is telling me they did more than see each other.
Huh? He's just happy because she
didn't go through with the audition.
だから オーディション受けなかったから 喜んでんだろ
絶対 何かあったって
I'm telling you, something happened!
何かって
Like what?
えっ まさか
本人に聞いてみる
You don't think...
I'm going to ask him!
バ バカ やめろ
I-Idiot! Don't!
真城君
Mashiro!
美保と何かいい事あったでしょ 顔に出てる
Something good happened between you and Miho, right?
It's written all over your face!
えっ 顔に うそ
On my face? No way!
何したの 白状しなさい
What did you do?
Confess!
何って 別に
Nothing, really.
うっそ 最低でも チューしてる そういう顔
No way!
You at least kissed, right?
えっ チュー してない してない マジで チューしてない
Your face gives it away!
Kiss? No, we didn't!
We really didn't!
正直に言っちゃいなさいよ
Just spill it, already!
手
Hands?
それだけ 手つないだだけ
That's all?
You just held hands?!
アッハッハ ２人らしいや つか 立派な進歩
That's just like you two.
Actually, that's great progress!
小学生か あんたらは
Are you two in grade school, or something?!
うるせな
Shut up.
俺たちの勝手じゃん
We can do what we want.
亜豆美保 許せません
Azuki Miho!
I won't forgive her!
オーディションを断った事 後悔させてあげます
I'll make her regret turning down the role!
声優も やっていけないようにして
I'll destroy her career as a voice actress!
亜城木夢叶も引きずり下ろします どんな手段でもいい
I'll drag Ashirogi Mutou down with her!
I don't care what it takes! Give me any ideas you have!
何か アイデアを出しなさい
真城君も 美保ちゃんも ふざけてるわけじゃない 一生懸命やってるんだ
Mashiro and Miho aren't messing around.
They're giving it their all.
あなた あの２人の味方
Are you on their side?
そういえば 「PCP」は あなたが立ち上げた マンガですものね
Come to think of it, PCP is a manga that you helped create.
僕は 「NATURAL」の担当 誰よりも 秋名愛子先生の力になりたいと思ってる
I'm NATURAL's editor!
I want to help you more than anyone else!
ほ 本当だ
It's true.
それに作家なら 作品内容で勝負すべきだ僕は その手助けしかできない
Besides, authors should compete
against each other with their works.
That's the only way I can help you.
なら 次の話のアイデアを出しなさい
Then come up with an idea for the next chapter!
服部さんは次々と出してくれました
Hattori gave me one after another!
さっ 早く
は はい えっと
Come on!
Right...
前 どこで終わりましたっけ
Um... where did we leave off last time?
そんな事も覚えてないんですか
You can't even remember that?
すいません
I'm sorry!
「PCP」３話目５位 「NATURAL」は
PCP's third chapter came in 5th place.
NATURAL is...
４位 「PCP」の上 これで秋名君少しは収まってくれるか
in 4th, right above PCP.
I wonder if Akina will calm down a bit when she hears this.
ん 先輩どうしたんですか
Hattori, what's wrong?
「PCP」３話目もいいじゃないですか
PCP's third chapter did well, didn't it?
亜城木君に早く教えてあげなきゃ
You have to hurry and tell Ashirogi!
ああ そうだな
Yeah, you're right.
３話目 ５位 普通なら これで上出来だが
The third chapter is in 5th.
Normally, this would be considered great, but...
半年だ
They have six months.
２５話までは 様子を見てやる
We'll see how it goes until their 25th chapter.
７話以降 打ち切られて当然の 順位なら即
If their ratings are too low by their seventh chapter, I won't hesitate to cancel it.
２５話までに 「CROW」「+NATURAL」に並べなければ そこで切る
And if they can't compete against CROW and NATURAL by their 25th chapter,
I'll cancel it then and there.
これでは駄目なんだ
This just isn't good enough.
最低でも 「+NATURAL」に半年で並ばないと
At the very least, we need to be even with +NATURAL within a half year.
これ以上 順位は下げられない
We can't afford to drop any lower than this.
Popular series! Ashirogi Mutou
PCP - Perfect Crime Party
何とかしなければ
I have to do something!
Popular series! Ashirogi Mutou
PCP - Perfect Crime Party
mogakinagara saikou no yume wo
The times when I fight and struggle and dream
katachi ni suru kono shunkan ga suki sa
of all the things I want in life is the best
tatakau you na te wo tsunagu you na
That's when I feel the bond between us and our strength to fight
kankaku ga shigekiteni da ne
Our view of the world overlaps and stimulates us
kousa shite
dakara motto migakou jibun rashiku arou
Let us polish ourselves, be more like how we should be
tsuzuita michi ni aru hazu
The future can be found on the path we walk
mirai wa
shinzuru mono ga chigau nakamatachi
My comrades believe in different things than me
Rival...and Friend!
butsukariau Pride
Our pride clashes
yuzurenai kore kara mo kokoro no mama susumou yo
I can't give up on it, I have to do what my heart commands me to do
junbi wa dekita
I'm ready
ikki ni kakeagaru tame no
I've got the unbending pride
akiramenai Pride
to run to the top now
hisshi nanda yo suki dakara suki wo mune ni susumu n da
This is my only choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
donna ashita ga matteru ka shiranai
I don't know what tomorrow will be like
asu mo
But I know that tomorrow, again,
bokura wa
girigiri
ganbatteru darou
we will do our best to get by
やっと新連載始まったのに 厳しい条件を突きつけられた
Next Time
Preview
Our new serialization has finally started up,
but we've been given some strict conditions!
ライバル達が頑張ってる中 俺たちはその条件をクリアできるのか
Can we overcome them, even while our rivals work against us?
次回 毎晩と融合 夢を繋げるためには努力しかない
Next time: Every Night and Unite.
Every Night and
Unite
Only hard work can connect our dreams!